<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Diamonds&amp;Hearts</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="next_turn_">Next turn</string>
    <string name="instruction">Instruction</string>
    <string name="match_instructions">Type in a new word for the data in this game, then hit done.</string>
    <string name="continue_str">Continue</string>
    <string name="guesser_prompt">This has not been set.</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="leave">Leave</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="turn_counter">Turn counter</string>
    <string name="quick_game">Quick Game</string>
    <string name="new_game">New Game</string>
    <string name="check_games">Check Games</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome,&#160;</string>
    <string name="diamond_label">&#9830;: </string>
    <string name="heart_label">&#9829;: </string>
    <string name="diamond">&#9830;</string>
    <string name="heart">&#9829;</string>
    <string name="spade">&#9824;</string>
    <string name="club">&#9827;</string>
    <string name="draw">Draw</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="appicon">AppIcon</string>
    <string name="rankings">Rankings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_instruction">Instruction</string>
    <string name="instruction_text">Players have a hand of cards to play in each game. Cards have 1-3 actions and 0-2 effects. These actions on a card will take place when the card is played. Whenever there is no card for a player, he might press \"skip\" that turn to gain 4 diamonds. By that, they could press \"draw\" to buy a card with cost of 3 diamonds.\n\n
If a card with a Clubs or Spades action is played, the player is prompted to choose which player to target. This may happen multiple times on a single card.\n\n
Action modifiers will stay with the player until they take effect or the game ends. Clever timing of events and their corresponding actions make up most of the game\'s strategy.\n\n
As for cards, the rules for actions have the followings:\n\n
1. N of Hearts will heal the player N hearts\n
2. N of Clubs will attack a chosen player for N damage\n
3. N of Diamonds calls for N diamonds to be put on the table\n
4. N of Spades will Steal N diamonds from a chosen player\n\n
As for cards, the rules for effects have the followings:\n
1. Extra turn - the player may play another card or draw a card\n
2. Extra card - the player will obtain an extra card at the end of a turn\n
3. Skip turn - the player\'s next turn is skipped\n
4. Shield - protects the player from the next attack\n
5. Drain - the player\'s next Club card steals the target\'s Hearts\n
6. Barter - the players next diamond payment is halved\n
7. Load - the player\'s next diamond payment is doubled\n
8. Strength - the player\'s next Club card does double damage\n
9. Weaken - the player\'s next Club card does half damage\n
10. Stealth - the player\'s next Spade card steals twice as much\n
11. Guilty - the player\'s next Spade card steals nothing\n
12. Fortitude - the player\'s next Heart card heals twice as much\n
13. Curse - the player\'s next Heart card will do damage to himself instead\n
14. Reaction - the player\'s next Club card will do damage target and himself\n</string>

</resources>